

DELANOVIĆ **NUDŽEJM**

+387-63-816-277

njmdelan@gmail.com

Mostar, Bosnia and Herzegovina

in @nudzejmdelanovic

https://github.com/itsNudzo

PROFILE

I'm passionate software developer, oriented towards backend development, a quick learner and willing to put in the hard work and dedication required to succeed. Experienced working in a team of multiple developers and having open conversations about problems and solutions in development.

EDUCATION

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

FACULTY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES

- Bachelor's Degree (180 ECTS)
- major: Software Development
- duration: 3 years
- · status: final year

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

SOFT SKILLS

NOVEMBER 2021 - JANUARY 2022
C++ PROGRAMMING COURSE

JUNE 2022

WORDPRESS COURSE

communicationcollaboration

critical thinking

· public speech

teamwork

problem-solving

multitasking

adaptibility

SKILLS

- C#
- C++
- Python
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- HTML
- CSS

- SQLite, MSSQL, PostgreSQL
- · Git. Github
- Postman, Swagger
- Open Api
- XUnit
- SOLID principles
- Design patterns

EXPERIENCE

MARCH 2023 - JUNE 2023

BACKEND DEVELOPER INTERN AT UXV CENTER GMBH

Ebikon, Switzerland (remote)

- I worked in C#, used .Net5+ frameworks, learned how to use SOLID principles and a few Design Patterns.
- I also learned how to use MSSQL and PostgreSQL with Entity Framework.
- Focusing on web development I learned Swagger and Postman technologies and XUnit testing.
- Working in team I mastered Git usage and finding different solutions for various problems.

APRIL 2024 - JULY 2024

PYTHON DEVELOPER INTERN AT FACTORY OF INNOVATIONS

2 Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina (remote)

https://factoryofinnovations.com/

- I worked in Python and Typescript, learned how to use Cloudflare Workers platform and Slack app.
- I have learned aforementioned technologies through parsing HTML. You can see some of those tasks on my GitHub.
- · I have also used Postman for API testing.

LANGUAGES

- Bosnian (native)
- English (C2)
- German (B1)

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- 1st place FIT Coding Challenge v.16
 - Category: Game Development